truckviewtv.com 2015-11-07

# Privacy Policy | TruckViewTV

[vc_row][vc_column width=”1/1″][vc_column_text]Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.truckviewtv.com and truckviewtv and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to truckviewtv include www.truckviewtv.com and truckviewtv. The truckviewtv website is a News and information site. By using the truckviewtv website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information  
truckviewtv may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase truckviewtv’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. truckviewtv may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age and gender. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by truckviewtv. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the truckviewtv website.

truckviewtv encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from truckviewtv so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. truckviewtv is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the truckviewtv website.

Use of your Personal Information  
truckviewtv collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

truckviewtv may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from truckviewtv and its affiliates. truckviewtv may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

truckviewtv does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

truckviewtv may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. truckviewtv may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to truckviewtv, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

truckviewtv may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within truckviewtv, in order to determine what truckviewtv services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within truckviewtv to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

truckviewtv will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on truckviewtv or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of truckviewtv; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of truckviewtv, or the public.

Security of your Personal Information  
To secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, truckviewtv uses the following:

cloudflare.com

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

Children Under Thirteen  
truckviewtv does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

Disconnecting your truckviewtv Account from Third Party Websites  
You will be able to connect your truckviewtv account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR TRUCKVIEWTV ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may learn how to disconnect their accounts from third-party websites by visiting their “My Account” page. Users may also contact us via email or telephone..

Opt-Out & Unsubscribe  
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from truckviewtv by contacting us here:  
– Web page: truckviewtv.com  
– Email: fb@truckviewtv.com

Changes to this Statement  
truckviewtv will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. truckviewtv encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how truckviewtv is protecting your information.

Contact Information  
truckviewtv welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that truckviewtv has not adhered to this Statement, please contact truckviewtv at:

truckviewtv

Email Address:  
fb@truckviewtv.com

Effective as of May 01, 2014[/vc_column_text][/vc_column][/vc_row]
